Well, Possum knows better than to be up on this couch but I asked her to get on this couch for this exercise.
Possum, you know better than getting up here, right?
Get down.
Good girl!
Good girl, you did good girl, come her, come here.
Are you allowed up here?
No, you're not.
We know better than to get up on the couch, don't we?
I came here and she had scraped up the leather really bad and I was so upset.
I brought her in here and I made her get up her and then I said no.
Now, she doesn't get up here without permission.
You might have to train your dog in this fashion over and over or with a clap of then hands that will frighten them a little bit from getting up there.